[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0100_d_00_container_getoffbeach",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@title_getoffbeach",
        "Description": "@desc_getoffbeach",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@proposal_getoffbeach",
        "InProgressResponse": "@incomplete_getoffbeach",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0600_0101_getoffbeach_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0101_culldrowned",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0101_d_00_container_culldrowned",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_culldrowned",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0101_culldrowned_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0101_culldrowned_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0102_campandtools",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0102_d_00_container_campandtools",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0102_campandtools_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0102_campandtools_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0102_campandtools_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0102_campandtools_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0102_campandtools_incomplete",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0102_campandtools_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0102_campandtools_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0103_boarproblem",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0103_d_00_container_boarproblem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarproblem",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_campandtools",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0103_boarproblem_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0103_boarproblem_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0104_xmarksthespot",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0104_d_00_container_xmarksthespot",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_xmarksthespot_p1",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0104_xmarksthespot_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0104_xmarksthespot_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0107_preciouscargo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0107_d_00_container_preciouscargo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_preciouscargo",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0107_preciouscargo_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0107_preciouscargo_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0601_0108_introtosettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0601_0108_d_00_container_introtosettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0604_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0601_0108_introtosettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0601_0108_introtosettlement_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0625_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0625_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistWW_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0625_0101_truffles_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0101_warnthemagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0101_d_00_container_warnthemagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0101_warnthemagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0101_warnmagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0101_warnmagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0101_warnmagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0101_warnmagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0606_0102_hearthandhome",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0606_0102_d_00_container_hearthandhome",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_hearthhome",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_warnmagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0606_0102_hearthandhome_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0606_0102_hearthandhome_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0102_intrototrader",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0102_d_00_container_intrototrader",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototrader",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0102_intrototrader_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0102_intrototrader_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0102_introtooverseer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0102_d_00_container_introtooverseer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0604_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0102_introtooverseer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0102_introtooverseer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0104_overseersettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0104_d_00_container_overseersettlement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0604_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_overseersettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtooverseer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0104_overseersettlement_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0104_overseersettlement_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0103_introtoartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0103_d_00_container_introtoartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0605_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0103_introtoartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0103_introtoartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0605_0101_craftforartificer",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0605_0101_d_00_container_craftforartificer",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0605_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_craftforartificer",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0605_0101_craftforartificer_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0605_0101_craftforartificer_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0605_0102_campingunlock",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0605_0102_d_00_container_campingunlock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_campingunlock",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0605_0102_campingunlock_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0605_0102_campingunlock_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0201_survivalistquest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0201_survivalistquest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0201_survivalistquest_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0201_d_00_container_survivalistquest_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_magistratequest",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0201_survivalistquest_V2_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0201_survivalistquest_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0202_returntomagistrate",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0202_d_00_container_returntomagistrate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntomagistrate",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0202_returntomagistrate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0202_returntomagistrate_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0202_introtoallfactions",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0202_d_00_container_introtoallfactions",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0202_introtoallfactions_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0609_0103_timetochoose",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0202_introtoallfactions_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0607_0101_marauderquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0607_0101_d_00_container_marauderquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0607_Commander",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0607_0101_marauderquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_M_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0607_0101_marauderquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0608_0101_syndicatequest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0608_0101_d_00_container_syndicatequest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0608_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0608_0101_syndicatequest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_S_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0608_0101_syndicatequest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0609_0101_covenantquest1",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0609_0101_d_00_container_covenantquest1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0609_Adjudicator",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0609_0101_covenantquest1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9806_C_0001_RankUp",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": true,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0609_0101_covenantquest1_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0609_0103_timetochoose",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 6,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0609_0103_d_00_container_timetochoose",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_timetochoose",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_introtoallfactions",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0609_0103_timetochoose_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0609_0103_timetochoose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0609_0103_timetochoose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0609_0103_timetochoose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0609_0103_timetochoose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0609_0103_timetochoose_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0401_factionhandoff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0401_d_00_container_factionhandoff",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0401_factionhandoff_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0602_0401_factionhandoff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0401_factionhandoff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0401_factionhandoff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0401_factionhandoff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0401_factionhandoff_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0501_encroachingcorruption",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0501_d_00_container_encroachingcorruption",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_encroachingcorruption",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0604_0799_TheHermitWW",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0501_encroachingcorruption_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0101_apricklyrequest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0101_d_00_container_apricklyrequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0610_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0101_apricklyrequest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0101_apricklyrequest_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0203_abominableluck",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0203_d_00_container_abominableluck",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0604_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0203_abominableluck_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0203_abominableluck_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc4"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0605_0301_soiledexpectations",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0605_0301_d_00_container_soiledexpectations",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0605_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_factionhandoff",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0605_0301_soiledexpectations_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0605_0301_soiledexpectations_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0302_predatorprey",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0302_d_00_container_predatorprey",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0302_predatorprey_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0302_predatorprey_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0103_thelonelyharvest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0103_d_00_container_thelonelyharvest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0610_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0103_thelonelyharvest_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0202_buildingblocks",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0202_d_00_container_buildingblocks",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0904_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_20",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0202_buildingblocks_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0202_buildingblocks_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc4"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0503_warpandweft",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0503_d_00_container_warpandweft",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0602_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0503_warpandweft_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0503_warpandweft_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0102_piratesofspice",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0102_d_00_container_piratesofspice",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0610_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0102_piratesofspice_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0102_piratesofspice_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0204_bearscratchrock",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0204_d_00_container_bearscratchrock",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0204_bearscratchrock_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0204_bearscratchrock_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0605_0401_jarofblackbile",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0605_0401_d_00_container_jarofblackbile",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0605_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0605_0401_jarofblackbile_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0605_0401_jarofblackbile_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0603_0301_makingsparks",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0603_0301_d_00_container_makingsparks",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0603_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_17",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0603_0301_makingsparks_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0603_0301_makingsparks_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0504_fabricnegotiation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0504_d_00_container_fabricnegotiation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1202_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0504_fabricnegotiation_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0605_0501_azothfulminate",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0605_0501_d_00_container_azothfulminate",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0605_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0605_0501_azothfulminate_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0605_0501_azothfulminate_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "WindswardArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0201_stevenexpedition",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0201_d_00_container_stevenexpedition",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0404_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0201_stevenexpedition_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0604_0202_happyreturns",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0201_stevenexpedition_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0202_happyreturns",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0202_d_00_container_happyreturns",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0604_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0604_0202_happyreturns_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0202_happyreturns_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0202_happyreturns_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0202_happyreturns_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0604_0202_happyreturns_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0604_0202_happyreturns_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0611_0101_ancientobservations",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0611_0101_d_00_container_ancientobservations",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0611_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0611_0101_ancientobservations_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0611_0101_ancientobservations_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0501_takentotask",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0501_d_00_container_takentotask",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0611_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0501_takentotask_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0602_0501_takentotask_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0501_takentotask_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0501_takentotask_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0501_takentotask_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0501_takentotask_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0501_takentotask_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0201_d_00_container_shotacrossbow_p1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p1_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0201_d_00_container_shotacrossbow_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p2_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0610_0201_d_00_container_shotacrossbow_p3",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0610_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0610_0201_shotacrossbow_p3_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0602_0502_oftheheart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0602_0502_d_00_container_oftheheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0601_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0602_0502_oftheheart_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0602_0502_oftheheart_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0622_1501_intrototravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0622_1501_d_00_container_intrototravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0422_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_intrototravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0622_1501_intrototravel_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0622_1502_returntravel",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0622_1501_intrototravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0622_1502_returntravel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0622_1502_d_00_container_returntravel",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0622_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_returntravel",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0622_1502_returntravel_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0622_1502_returntravel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0622_1502_returntravel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0622_1502_returntravel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0622_1502_returntravel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0622_1502_returntravel_complete_availaible_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0623_0101_FQ01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0623_0101_d_00_container_FQ01",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0623_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0101_FQ01_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0623_0101_FQ1_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0623_0101_FQ1_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0623_0101_FQ1_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0623_0101_FQ1_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0623_0101_FQ1_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0623_0101_FQ1_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0623_0102_FQ02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0623_0102_d_00_container_FQ02",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0423_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0102_FQ02_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0623_0102_FQ02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@6023_0102_FQ02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@6023_0102_FQ02_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@6023_0102_FQ02_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0623_0102_FQ02_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0623_0102_FQ02_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0423_0101_FQ03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0423_0101_d_00_container_FQ03",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0923_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0423_0101_FQ03_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0423_0101_FQ03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0423_0101_FQ03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0423_0101_FQ03_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0423_0101_FQ03_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0423_0101_FQ03_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0423_0101_FQ03_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0923_0101_FQ04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0923_0101_d_00_container_FQ04",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1223_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0923_0101_FQ04_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0923_0101_FQ04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0923_0101_FQ04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0923_0101_FQ04_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0923_0101_FQ04_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0923_0101_FQ04_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0923_0101_FQ04_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1223_0101_FQ05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1223_0101_d_00_container_FQ05",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1023_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1223_0101_FQ05_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1223_0101_FQ05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1223_0101_FQ05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1223_0101_FQ05_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1223_0101_FQ05_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1223_0101_FQ05_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1223_0101_FQ05_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1023_0101_FQ06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1023_0101_d_00_container_FQ06",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0223_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1023_0101_FQ06_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1023_0101_FQ06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1023_0101_FQ06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1023_0101_FQ06_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1023_0101_FQ06_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1023_0101_FQ06_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1023_0101_FQ06_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0223_0101_FQ07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0223_0101_d_00_container_FQ07",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1323_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0223_0101_FQ07_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0223_0101_FQ07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0223_0101_FQ07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0223_0101_FQ07_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0223_0101_FQ07_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0223_0101_FQ07_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0223_0101_FQ07_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1323_0101_FQ08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1323_0101_d_00_container_FQ08",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1323_0101_FQ08_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1323_0101_FQ08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1323_0101_FQ08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1323_0101_FQ08_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1323_0101_FQ08_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1323_0101_FQ08_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1323_0101_FQ08_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1523_0101_FQ09",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1523_0101_d_00_container_FQ09",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1123_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1523_0101_FQ09_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1523_0101_FQ09_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1523_0101_FQ09_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1523_0101_FQ09_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1523_0101_FQ09_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1523_0101_FQ09_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1523_0101_FQ09_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1123_0101_FQ10",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 45,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1123_0101_d_00_container_FQ10",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0324_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1123_0101_FQ10_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1123_0101_FQ10_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1123_0101_FQ10_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1123_0101_FQ10_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1123_0101_FQ10_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1123_0101_FQ10_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1123_0101_FQ10_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1424_0101_FQ11",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0324_0101_d_00_container_FQ12",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1424_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1424_0101_FQ11_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@1424_0101_FQ11_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1424_0101_FQ11_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1424_0101_FQ11_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1424_0101_FQ11_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1424_0101_FQ11_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1424_0101_FQ11_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0324_0101_FQ12",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1424_0101_d_00_container_FQ11",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0724_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0324_0101_FQ12_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0324_0101_FQ12_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0324_0101_FQ12_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0324_0101_FQ12_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0324_0101_FQ12_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0324_0101_FQ12_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0324_0101_FQ12_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0724_0101_FQ13",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0724_0101_d_00_container_FQ13",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0823_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0724_0101_FQ13_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0724_0101_FQ13_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0724_0101_FQ13_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0724_0101_FQ13_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0724_0101_FQ13_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0724_0101_FQ13_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0724_0101_FQ13_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0823_0101_FQ14",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0823_0101_d_00_container_FQ14",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0823_0101_FQ14_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0823_0101_FQ14_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0823_0101_FQ14_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0823_0101_FQ14_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0823_0101_FQ14_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0823_0101_FQ14_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0823_0101_FQ14_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0523_0101_FQ15",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0523_0101_d_00_container_FQ15",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0523_0101_FQ15_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0523_0101_FQ15_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0523_0101_FQ15_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0523_0101_FQ15_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0523_0101_FQ15_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0523_0101_FQ15_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0523_0101_FQ15_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0604_0799_TheHermitWW",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0604_0799_container_TheHermitWW",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_MSQ_TheHermit_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0604_0799_TheHermitWW_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_0604_02_Overseer",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_9901_TheHermit_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0611_0102_SeeingClearly",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0611_0102_d_00_container_SeeingClearly",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0611_Stranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0611_0102_SeeingClearly_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_title",
        "Description": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0611_0102_SeeingClearly_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0699_0103_d_00_container_BarkimedesPup",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_title",
        "Description": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0101_Barkimedes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0699_0101_d_00_container_Barkimedes",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_title",
        "Description": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0699_0102_d_00_container_Barkimedes2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_success",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_title",
        "Description": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_06_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0601_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0601_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0602_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0602_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0603_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0603_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0604_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0604_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0605_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0605_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0606_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0606_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0607_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0607_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0608_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0608_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0609_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0609_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0610_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0610_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0601_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0601_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0602_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0602_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0603_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0603_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0604_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0604_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0605_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0605_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0606_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0606_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0607_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0607_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0608_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0608_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0609_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0609_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0610_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0610_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0601_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0601_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0602_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0602_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0603_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0603_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0604_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0604_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0605_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0605_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0606_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0606_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0607_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0607_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0608_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0608_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0609_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0609_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0610_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0610_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0661_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0661_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0662_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0662_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0663_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0663_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0664_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0664_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0665_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0665_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0666_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0666_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0667_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0667_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0668_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0668_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0669_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0669_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0670_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0670_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0661_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0661_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0662_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0662_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0663_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0663_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0664_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0664_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0665_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0665_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0666_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0666_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0667_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0667_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0668_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0668_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0669_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0669_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0670_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0670_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0661_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0661_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0662_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0662_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0663_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0663_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0664_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0664_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0665_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0665_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0666_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0666_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0667_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0667_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0668_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0668_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0669_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0669_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0670_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0670_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_06_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_06_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": false,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]